Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The store workers security plan, 1956; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Second copy
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: The 65 Pension plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The 65 Security Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The 65 Security Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Labor Health Institute, Inc.: quality of service, 1948; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry G. Farish
  - Item 6: What happens to your union dollars?, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Take care of your teeth, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Flyer
  - Item 8: LHI - Service when you need it, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Flyer. 2 Copies
  - Item 9: Protect your family's health, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Your health, a manual for the members of the, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 1)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU)., Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Labor Health Insitute is on its way., Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Aims and purposes of the Labor Health Institute, 1946; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 2)
    Author: Elmer Richman
    Notes: 2 copies
  - Item 3: The Labor Health Institute - a plan for health service, 1946; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Labor sponsored health plans, 1946; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: LHI - Labor Health Institute, Inc. --- chart, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 2)
- New York Hotel Trades Council, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your insurance plan, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Hotel and Club Employees Union, Local 6, AFL-CIO --packet, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Esta es su Union: bienvenidos al Local 6, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 3)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 4: como y donde buscar un empleo, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 3)
    Author: New York Hotel Trades Council; Hotel Association of New York City
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU)., Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Shop steward manual, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Twenty Five years of progress - 1939-1964, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 4)
- United Mail Order, Warehouse and Retail Employees Union, Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Avery formula, 1944; Publication (Box 319.1, Folder 5)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Jewish conspiracy, 1944; Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
    Author: Max Nomad
  - Item 2: Your welfare fund benefits, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: For the union makes us strong, 1948; Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Local 260's Cushman's Health and Welfare Fund for employee Members, 1961; Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your program of insurance, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Victory without strike, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
    Notes: flyers/posters
  - Item 7: NewsFull pay while attending retirement preparation course during working hours, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Willmark Spies, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Facts you should know, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Look at the record, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The following telegram, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Calling the shots!!!, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Propaganda, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Complaints..., Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Union Benefits, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Our Guarantee, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Stop and think, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Inventory time, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Let's analyze, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Arbitration, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Appreciation!, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Our record, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Extra Extra Extra, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Local 474 - CIO looks ahead, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Getting the facts, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: A message from your friends in Safeway, Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Union program features full pay wile attending retirement preparation course during working hours and complete physical checkups, 1964; Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
    Notes: Press Release
  - Item 28: Unionize, 1950; Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no. 27-28 (1950)
  - Item 29: Correspondence, 1962; Publication (Box 320, Folder 1)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Local 1199 Drug Pension Plan, 1971; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Local 1199 Hospital Pension Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The New York Times Magazine, 1970; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
    Notes: 22-Mar- 70
  - Item 4: Directory of Union Officers - Whos Who in 1199, 1975; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Fact sheet., Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The member and the union, Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
    Author: Leon J. Davis
    Notes: Article
  - Item 7: Let's get organized, Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Some trade union basics, Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The new right: all wrong for labor, 1978; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Jan. 1978 issue of 1199 News
  - Item 10: The woman from 1199, 1975; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Let's find out how hospitals spend their money, Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
    Author: Moe Foner
  - Item 12: 1199 News - A Special Issue -- Working in hospitals: then and now, 1976; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Local 1199, Drug and Hospital Union, 1973; Publication (Box 320, Folder 2)
    Author: Al Nash
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1199 drug news, 1959; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jun-59
  - Item 2: 1199 drug news, 1960; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
    Notes: July/Aug 1960
  - Item 3: 1199 drug news, 1963; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
    Notes: May-63
  - Item 4: The Modern Hospital, 1965; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
    Notes: Aug-65
  - Item 5: 1199 Drug News - Twenty Fifth Anniv. Issue, 1957; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jun- 57
  - Item 6: Report of the hospital workers, poorly paid aides unite to fight health establishment, 1971; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Hospital union oks rocky pact, 1962; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Correspondence, 1974; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Local 1199 Benefit plan, Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: WCBS-TV News - transcript of broadcast - Guest Leon J. Davis, Pres. Local 1199, 1962; Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The case for union recognitiion in voluntary hospitals, Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: In the matter of the arbitration conducted pursuant to Section 716 of the Labor Law, Publication (Box 320, Folder 3)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Know your union: Local 1199, Constitution, 1961; Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The New York Times Magazine, 1970; Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 22, 1970. Second copy
  - Item 3: consideremos los sueldos y las condiciones de trabajo en los hospitales, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Let's talk about the wages and working conditions in voluntary hospitals, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Plan A 1199 Health Benefits, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: A woman's place is in her union, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Union drive sweeping thru hospitals, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Hospital workers need a union, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Extra! Hospital workers win union rights in New State Law, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: They said it couldn't be done, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: An appeal to reason - How to avoid another Hospital strike, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: The victory at montefiore all hospital workers need a union now!, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: The many faces of District 1199: a booklet for new members of the Guild Division, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: The many faces of District 1199: a booklet for new members, Publication (Box 320, Folder 4)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU)., Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A summary of collective bargaining: the San Francisco Retailers' Council and Department Store Employers' Union, Local 1100, 1949; Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
    Author: Robert L. Raschen
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Camera, action!, 1968; Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Call to the Tenth Convention, 1966; Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: President's report to the tenth convention, 1966; Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Automation in retailing and distribution, 1960; Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Call to the ninth Convention, 1962; Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Union members are everywhere, Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Your secret weapon, Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Don't buy any Seagram's Products, Publication (Box 320, Folder 5)
- Montgomery Ward, Publication (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Investigation of communism in New York City distributive trades, 1948; Publication (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Consider the Woolworth workers, 1940; Publication (Box 320, Folder 6)
    Author: Therese Mitchell
  - Item 3: Report to the Congress of Industrial Organizations on labor conditions in Bolivia, 1943; Publication (Box 320, Folder 6)
    Author: Martin J. Kyne
  - Item 4: Organizer's manual: Montgomery Ward Organizing Committee, Publication (Box 320, Folder 6)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). St. Louis Joint Board, Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Joint Council Steward at work: a handbook for Joint Council Shop Stewards, 1945; Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Let's look at our union: it's aims, activities, accomplishments, 1945; Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Wolchok Union supplanted on CIO order, 1948; Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
    Notes: news clippings
  - Item 4: Labor Health Institute Pioneers in low cost medical care for workers, 1947; Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
    Author: Kenneth A. Brent
  - Item 5: 10-N-10 Drive, Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Gaining a perspective, Publication (Box 321, Folder 1)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). St. Louis Joint Board, Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: RWDSU Record, 1957; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: Feb. 17, 1957
  - Item 2: The Shoe Reporter, 1947; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1947-Mar-Apr, Oct-Nov
  - Item 3: The Shoe Reporter, 1948; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1948-June, Sept, Oct
  - Item 4: The Shoe Reporter, 1949; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1949-Jan, Sept
  - Item 5: The Shoe Reporter, 1950; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1950-Feb
  - Item 6: The Shoe Reporter, 1951; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1951-Jan
  - Item 7: The Shoe Reporter, 1952; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1952-Feb
  - Item 8: The Shoe Reporter, 1955; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1955-May, Sept, Dec
  - Item 9: The Shoe Reporter, 1956; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1956-June, Nov
  - Item 10: The Shoe Reporter, 1957; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1957-Jan, Dec
  - Item 11: The Shoe Reporter, 1958; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1958-Mar
  - Item 12: The Shoe Reporter, 1959; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1959-Mar, May
  - Item 13: The Shoe Reporter, 1960; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1960-Jan, Mar, Sept, Nov
  - Item 14: The Shoe Reporter, 1961; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1961-Jan, Dec
  - Item 15: The Shoe Reporter, 1962; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1962- Jan, Mar, Sept
  - Item 16: The Shoe Reporter, 1963; Publication (Box 321, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1963-Jan
- United Slate, Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers' Association, Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: National pattern for local apprenticeship standards in the roofing industry, 1946; Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Roster of local unions: officers, union officers, office hours, phone numbers, date of meetings, meeting place, 1951; Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Annuity Fund: Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers' Association, 1961; Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers' Association: health and welfare plan, 1963; Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Union Voice, 1963; Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
    Notes: Mar-63
  - Item 6: Joint Trainee Program, 1957; Publication (Box 321, Folder 3)
- United Slate, Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers' Association. Local Union No. 8 (New York, NY), Publication (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Pension fund: Composition Roofers, Damp & Waterproof Workers' Association, Local No. 8, 1959; Publication (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The closed or open shop-which?: being a preachment, 1905; Publication (Box 321, Folder 4)
    Author: Elbert Hubbard
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 1970 URW Welfare Agreement: explanations, recommended procedures and 1970 negotiated benefits, Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Outline: URW-SUB, 1968; Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Goodyear section of International Policy Committee, United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastics Workers of America, 1959; Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: First amended agreement on supllemental unemployment benefits, 1959; Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Grievance No. 15-3D, 1964; Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Arbitration, 1964; Publication (Box 321, Folder 5)
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1949; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Delivered by L. S. Buckmaster, President, 1953; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
    Author: L. S. Buckmaster
  - Item 3: Peter Bommarito, 1970; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Community Service Programs for treatment of Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, 1975; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: A convenient reference directory entitled "Human Resoure Index"., 1975; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Join URW Ladies' Auxiliaries, 1968; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: URW Labor Contract - District 6 Council Meeting, 1964; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Address of L.S. Buckmaster.Social and economic implications of the pension drive, 1949; Publication (Box 322, Folder 1)
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Washington Report - Seventh Annual URW Washington Legislative Institutes, 1958; Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A mighty fine union, Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: If your biggest union problem is.How to reach the rank and file., 1956; Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: If your biggest union problem is.How to reach the rank and file., 1957; Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: URCLPWA Legislative Institute, 1952; Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Propaganda and you, 1959; Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: How to reach the union member, 1958; Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Collective bargaining for 1955, Publication (Box 322, Folder 2)
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America (URW), Publication (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Shop Steward: key to a strong union, Publication (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: United Rubber Worker, 1955; Publication (Box 322, Folder 3)